&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，让我们谈谈这个模块的练习，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right, let's talk about this module's exercise,
我们将逐步解决这个问题。
we'll walk through a solution to it.
正如ReadMe所展示的那样，您希望采用这些功能，即
As the ReadMe lays out, you want to take these functions, the ones that are at
底部，并实质上将它们包装在一个称为定义工作坊的大函数中。
the bottom, and essentially wrap them in one big function called define workshop.
这将是我们的模块工厂功能。
That'll be our module factory function.
所以我会从这个开始，我会说定义工作坊。
So I'll start by doing that, I'll say defineWorkshop.
这个大函数将包括它里面的所有这些。
And this one big function is going to include all of these inside of it.
所以就像其他的一样，
And so just like with the other ones,
我会将这些函数保持在该作用域的底部。
I'll keep those functions at the bottom of that scope.
我将创建并返回一个公共API。
I'm gonna make and return a public API.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：然后我还需要一些数据供这个模块关闭使用。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then I also need some data for this module to close over to use.
我将要关闭的数据是currentEnrollment和
And the data that I'm gonna be closing over is currentEnrollment and
StudentRecords，我需要这两个数组在这里。
studentRecords, I need those two arrays Inside of here.
因此，我将创建并安排名为currentEnrollment，
So I will make and arrange called currentEnrollment,
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：另一个叫
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Another one called
StudentRecords，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：在我的公共API上，
studentRecords, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: On my public API,
我需要根据ReadMe
I need to have according to the ReadMe,
这五个函数是addStudent和regilStudents。
these five functions, addStudent and enrollStudents.
所以，让我们先做这些，然后定义那些。
So, let's do those first and define those.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这些是如何工作的？
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: How do those work?
好的，首先，我们有addStudent。
Well, first, we have addStudent.
它将采取的ID，姓名和他们是否支付和
It's gonna take the ID, the name and whether they're paid and
创建一个记录并将其填入其中。
create a record and stuff that in.
所以，我们要记下身份，姓名，
So, we're gonna take id, name,
并作为输入付费。
and paid as the input.
我们将进入学生记录
And we're going to push into the studentRecords
数组，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：一个对象
array, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: An object that
包括id，name和payed。
includes id, name, and paid.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：EnrollStudent类似，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: EnrollStudent is similar,
entrlStudent，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：接受学生ID，
enrollStudent, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Takes a student id,
并将其推送到currentEnrollment数组中。
and it pushes that into the currentEnrollment array.
我要做一个额外的检查，因为这是一个API现在而不是被设置，
I'm gonna do one extra check since this is an API now rather than being set up,
这是我要做一个额外的检查，以确保我没有试图添加
it's I'm gonna do an extra check that makes sure that I'm not try to add
将ID复制到数组中。
duplicate IDs into the array.
所以我会做的如果
So I will do if
(！currentEnrollment.includes(Id)，和
(!currentEnrollment.includes(id), and
currentEnrollment.push(Id)。
currentEnrollment.push(id).
自述文件然后说我们需要一个printCurrentEnrollment。
ReadMe then says we need a printCurrentEnrollment.
那么printCurrenEregilment会做什么呢？
So what would printCurrenEenrollment do?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：它不需要任何输入，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: It doesn't take any inputs,
它本质上取代了这个调用。
it essentially takes the place of this call.
这个正在打印currentEnrollment，所以
This one is printing the currentEnrollment, so
让我们从字面上将其复制到printCurrentEnrollment中。
let's literally just copy that into our printCurrentEnrollment.
我们不希望他们提供自己的ID列表，
We don't want them to provide their own list of IDs,
因为这就是模块的全部目的是抽象细节和
because that's the whole purpose of the module is to abstract that detail and
把它作为隐藏的实现，好吗？
keep it as a hidden implementation, okay?
接下来，自述文件说我们需要一个regilPaidStudents。
Next the readme says we need an enrollPaidStudents.
完全一样，entenlPaidStudents也在做同样的事情，
Exactly the same, enrollPaidStudents is doing the same thing as this,
也就是打电话给付费学生注册，并且
which is to call paid students to enroll, and
然后用它更新当前注册数组。
then update the current enrollment array with it.
那么，让我们做，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：什么是
So, let's do, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: What's
它再次调用了regilPaidStudent。
it called again, enrollPaidStudent.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：最后，我们需要提醒UnpaidStudents。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then finally, we need a remindUnpaidStudents.
再说一遍，这基本上就是取而代之的地方，
Again, that is basically taking the place,
用我们的currentEnrollment呼叫remindunpay。
of calling remindUnpaid with our currentEnrollment.
所以我们需要它，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：和一个函数。
So we need that, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And a function.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：所以我们现在已经将这些实现细节隐藏在一个模块中
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So we've now hidden those implementation details inside of a module
定义。
definition.
我们有，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：那么，
We have, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So,
我们公开了五个公共API方法，并将其他所有方法都保密。
we expose five public API methods and we keep everything else private.
我们保持数据的私密性，封闭性是我们随着时间的推移保持这种状态的方式。
We keep the data private, and closure is how we maintain that state over time.
那么，最后一步是&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：Setting(&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：设置
Last step, then, is instead of, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Setting
在这些数组上，我们需要实际创建和实例化，我猜不是
up these arrays we need to actually make and instantiate, I guess is not
最后一步是下一步，我们需要实例化我们的工作坊。
the last step but the next step, is we need to instantiate our workshop.
所以我们将调用define工作坊，并开始使用它。
So we're gonna call defineWorkshop, and we're gonna start using it.
我们先建立学生档案，
We'll first set up the student records,
所以我要去，因为我超级懒，
so I'm going to, because I'm super lazy,
使用一些正则表达式替换来定义这些。
use some regular expression replacing to define those.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我已经为自己写了一个
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I have one already written for myself so
我不需要重写。
I don't have to rewrite it.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我需要打开正则表达式模式。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I need to turn on regular expression mode.
好了，这些都是我的函数调用。
All right, so now those are all my function calls.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：然后类似地，在这里我们将调用Deep JS.entenlStudent。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And then similarly here we're gonna call deepJS.enrollStudent.
我就是这么叫的，对吧，招生？
That's what I called it, right, enrollStudent?
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：是的，&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：好的，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Yeah, &gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: All right,
我只是把这些打出来。
I'll just type these out.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：现在这些事情都做完了，剩下的就是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Now that stuff's done, and then all that's left is for
我们更新这些调用以打印，
us to update these calls to print,
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：PrintCurrentEnrollment。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: PrintCurrentEnrollment.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我想我错过了一个细节。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I think I missed a detail there.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我不仅需要更新它，而且
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I not only need to update it, but
我们需要打印记录，所以我错过了[INAUDIBLE]。
we need to print the records, so I missed that [INAUDIBLE].
我们的注册付费学生需要更新注册并打印这些记录。
Our enroll paid students needs to update the enrollment and print those records.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我们将其称为Deep JS.regilPaidStudents。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: We call deepJS.enrollPaidStudents.
最后但并非最不重要的是，ddeep JS.RemindUnpaidSStudents。
And then last but not least, ddeepJS.RemindUnpaidSstudents.
&GT；&GT；凯尔·辛普森：我们结束了。
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: And we're done.
正如我在开始时所说的，模块确实是最重要的代码之一
As I said at the outset, modules really is one of the most important code
所有JavaScript中的组织模式，可能是所有软件中的组织模式，
organization patterns in all of JavaScript, maybe in all of software,
但肯定是在所有JavaScript中。
but certainly in all of JavaScript.
所以你会从这个模式中得到很多好处，
So you're gonna get a lot of mileage out of thinking about this pattern,
练习它，尝试更多地实现它。
practicing it, trying to implement it more.
所以我会强烈推荐这门课的所有内容，但是
So I would strongly recommend everything in this course for sure but
尤其是这个。
especially this.
如果你愿意，试着回去做一些家庭作业。
Try to go back and do some homework, if you will.
试着回去找找
Try to go back and look for
代码中某个地方可以使用一些更好的组织和
some place in your code where that could use some better organization and
看看是否有一种方法可以提取出模块的简单定义。
see if there's a way to extract out a simple definition for a module.